{
    "id": "6e4aef3d11a1489386289e85b68fc331",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was amazed ……………………….. their brilliant performance.",
            "description": "Amaze is followed by the preposition at.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21e7472c9a1e44e693ec778d8512b30d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is afflicted ………………………. leprosy.",
            "description": "Afflict is followed by with.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0efc1967336742f09c9c28d4deb492e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alcohol does not agree ………………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f7170a62f75403fb820a87329740334"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ………………………… your bad behavior.",
            "description": "We write for after apologize.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9998ffaa0293437e81d3c367d0678740"
        },
        {
            "question": "She often boasts ………………………….. her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5d9cc725e9043708db067a19d54b202"
        },
        {
            "question": "One must not brood ………………………. one’s failures.",
            "description": "Brood is followed by over.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d66d26b9911847f8ac9f357ef8611e8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We called …………………………… them yesterday.",
            "description": "To call on is to visit.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02fc512fbc0c4e769f25e3bafac9ed89"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been charged …………………………… treason.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "848dfa72f1404d1a935e15bd555bb018"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not want to compete …………………….. anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "767d72de55c94d65851d5ca38ebff0f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The merchant deals …………………………. precious metals.",
            "description": "Deal in can mean sell.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c948ca2f9e474e7b8d7faf5c982e44db"
        },
        {
            "question": "One must not deviate …………………………. the path of truth and virtue.",
            "description": "Deviate is followed by from.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f4c0dd1c6514e3d97532ca4db5aed85"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has never shown any interest …………………….. politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ac0a43574c6a4631a49c19f48706752b"
        }
    ]
}